Operations teams drown in telemetry, alerts, and fragmented workflows.
BitsIO AgenticOps turns Splunk data into explainable AI decisions with human control.
Dashboard shows live incidents, confidence, approvals, and runtime status in one place.
In Incidents, every conclusion is transparent: evidence, correlation, reasoning, and policy checks.
Decision Gate enforces human approval with clear approve and reject paths.
Approvals centralizes pending decisions for fast, accountable review.
Monitoring provides platform health, latency, and runtime quality signals.
Telemetry Value Impact quantifies ingest waste and annual savings opportunities.
Fraud Risk Agent correlates payment, identity, and approval anomalies into explainable risk actions.
Settings lets teams switch local and cloud runtime profiles and validate connections safely.
BitsIO AgenticOps: faster response, lower waste, and safer decisions for SRE, SOC, Audit, and Risk teams.